好的 等一下 等一下
Okay, hold on, hold on.
很好
Nice.
拉斯穆森
Oh, Rasmussen?
嗨 嘿 汤姆  -嗨
Hi. Hey, Tom.   -Hi.
我...放桌上就好  -放这边吗
I... Just put it there.   -Put this here?
好
Okay
今天是选前之夜
So, it's election eve
猜猜 性爱圣诞老人 送了你什么东西
and guess what Father Sex mas has brought you?
是新鲜热烫的民调结果
Why, hot fresh polling
好的 希门尼斯领先四个点
Yeah. Jimenez up by four.
天啊 你打算怎么做
Jesus. How are you gonna play?
我猜 我也不知道
I guess, I don't know.
放大 以制造狂乱
Amplify to gin up our maniacs
或是否认 抹黑和掩盖吧
Or deny, shit on, and bury, I guess
是马特森  -他想干吗
Mats son.   -What does he want?
你知道的
Oh, you know.
他觉得生活+的热潮消退
He thinks the Living Plus stock bump is fading
想知道我哥有什么计划
and he wants to know what my brothers have cooking
他会来吗  -来派对吗 不会
Is he coming?   -To the party? No.
他说 他不想泡在我爸...
No, he doesn't wanna swim around my dad's
狗屁选前脑死 美国在线时代传统媒体
"bullshit pre-election brain dead AOL-era legacy media
老朽腐烂的滥交派对
putrid stuffed-mushroom fuck fest."
我还以为会很好玩呢
I thought it was gonna be fun
那么 送你一个派对小礼物
So, this is just a little party prezzie
因为你是个 性感的冒烟
for being such a hot piece of ass
谢谢  -又狐媚的小骚货
Thank you.   -and such a foxy little minx.
也借此表达
And, you know, just to say
我很高兴 能跟你一起主办这个派对
that I'm really glad that we're hosting this party together
是啊  -我们可以跟大家说
Yeah. .   -You know, we could say to people
我们暂时分开过
that we... had a little break
现在又复合了
and then we're back, you know?
好 这样说很好  -是的
Yeah. I like that.   -Yeah
什么  -没错
-What?   -Yeah.
是一只…蝎子
It's a... a scorpion.
为什么
Because?
因为...
Cause it's...
很好笑啊
it's funny.
因为…为什么
Because... why?
因为...这是个玩笑
Cause it's like... it's a joke
蝎子是谁
Who's the scorpion?
应该是你
You, I guess.
就是很傻气啊 宝贝 就是...
But it's just silly, honey. It's like, you know.
我爱你 但我们会相爱相杀
I love you, but you kill me, and I kill you, and you.
明白吗
You know?
好吧 是的 我懂了
Okay, yeah, right. No, yeah. I get it.
我喜欢  -那就好
-I like it.   -Good.
你得上班了  -对
-Well, you gotta get to work.   -Yeah
要为毒化作用 尽一己之力
You know, you gotta go contribute to the great toxification.
要尽我的本分
Gotta do my part.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
大家都还好吗  -我很好 我们都很好
How's everyone doing?   -No, I'm fine. We're all fine.
我们见面没关系 但如果是法律事务
And, you know, this is fine, but if it's legal stuff
我真的不能介入
I really need to keep my head out of that right now.
我觉得 我们还是...  -好
I'd rather keep it with just...  -Okay
让律师... 不是 我会长话短说
Iawyers, so...   -No. I wilI just keep this brief.
就是
It's.
苏菲不肯上学
Sophie doesn't wanna go to school.
大选让她很不安
She's... freaked out about the election.
什么意思 她还好吗 怎么…
What do you mean? What... is she okay? What...
怎么了  -她很好 只是…
What is it? What...   -She's okay. It's just...
是这样 周末的时候 上周末
All right, so, on the... the weekend, this weekend
有人
someone kind of...
她觉得... 在街上 有人推挤着 从她身边走过
She felt... pushed by her a little, on the street.
网上有一则留言 她觉得是…
But there was a comment that she felt came from the...
就是
It was.
好吧 那个人穿着一件雷文海德的T恤
All right, the guy had on a Raven head shirt
T恤上写了一句话 然后...
There was a quote on the shirt, and yeah
她认为那句话 带有种族歧视色彩 所以她很难过
She felt it was racially tinged, and she's been upset.
他们说什么了
What did they say?
我不知道
I don't know.
现在 学校里
And now, at school
有学生发起了 反泛美网科的行动
some kids have started this whole anti-ATN thing
其实是很支持苏菲
which is actually very supportive
但是 你知道 这…
but, you know, it's...
对她来说 很复杂
complex for her?
当时谁跟她在一起
Who was with her?
她为什么在街上
Why... Why was she out on the street?
她去第六大道干吗  -你在问我…
Sixth near MOMA?   -Did you just ask me
她为什么在街上吗  -对 有人...
-why she was on the street?   -Yeah, I mean, someone.
对 你说 有人推我们的女儿
You're telling me someone pushed our daughter
还是什么的  -有人推挤着 从她身边走过
or whatever.   -Pushed by her
当时她跟朋友在一起  -你在哪里
She was with her friends.   -Like, where were you?
我在哪里?  -对
Where was I?   -Yeah
你他妈认真的吗  -对 我不是怪你
-Are you fucking serious?   -I'm not blaming you.
我只是想 先知道所有信息
I'm just... I'm trying to get all the information
再决定要怎么做
before I make a decision on our course of action
你要决定  -对
You need Tomake a decision -And, so, yeah
要不要打电话给女儿...  -当时你在哪里
-if you're gonna call your...   -Where were you?
我在养我们的女儿
I was raising our daughter
而你他妈在经营一个  -行吧
-while you were fucking running -Oh, yeah
种族歧视的新闻组织  -行吧...很好
-a racist news organization.   -Yeah... Great
去你妈的 拜托...  -你骂我?
-Fuck you. Come on...   -Oh, fuck me?
你他妈 怎么敢 这么审问我
How fucking dare you interrogate me?
质问我如何教女儿  -我心里当然很难过
On how I parent?   -Obviously, I feel bad.
当然 我会不计一切
Obviously, I will do anything
保护她 不择手段  -这样吧
to protect her, anything,   -Okay, you know what?
好吧 我就先…
Okay. I'm gonna just end.
我们会处理的
We'll cope.
还有 我也不知道 你也许 可以打个电话给你女儿
And I don't know, just may be call your fucking daughter
我当然会打 天啊 拉瓦 天啊
Well, obviously. Jesus, Rava. Jesus
天啊 你以为我是什么样的家长
What kind of parent do you think I am?
你对我现在做的事 一无所知
You know, yoUhave no idea the things I'm doing
我现在参与的项目
the things I'm working on.
六个大陆 好吗
Six continents, okay?
我忙得要死要活 都是为了孩子们
I'm breaking my back, and it's all for them.
好吗 我想让世界更安全
Okay? Tomake the world safe.
继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 7 集
是 很好 我喜欢
Yeah, great. Dig on that
我爱死了 超爱
Dig to heck on that. Dig
对 不是的 我们很中意那笔交易
Yeah, no, we... we love the deal
我们只是要确保 对马特森和GoJo
We just have to make sure we know everything
已经了如指掌
on Mats son and GoJo.
我知道 要尽职调查
I mean, there's due diligence
但这 已经不只是尽职调查了
but this is, you know, un due diligence.
这是超越尽职了 好吗
Extra diligence, okay?
好极了 挖出马特森的丑事
Okay. great. And get that dirt on Mats son.
任何事都可能派上用场
Anything could be useful
看似不重要的细节 我都可能用得上
Apparently, insignificant details could be very useful Tome,
我们都能用
to us.
什么 不
What? No.
你他妈是个助理龟孙子
You're a fucking deputy rat fucker.
别不想当龟孙子 汤玛斯
Don't object to being a rat fucker, Tomas
这样很难看
It's unbecoming.
你好吗  -嘿 亲爱的
How you doing?   -Hey, honey
亲
Kiss?
很高兴看到你  -我也是
-Good to see you,   -Good to see you.
嗨  -嘿 你好吗
Hi.   -Hey. How you doing?
你好吗  -很好
-Good.   -Yeah.
我刚去看过老爸
I just came from seeing Pop
你又去了?
Again?
对  -有什么...变化吗
-Yeah.   -Well, any... change?
看起来很不错
Looking good
他今天没有下床气 天啊
Woke up on the right side of the coffin today, boy.
干吗 我喜欢去看他 你也该去看看他
What? I like to go. You should go.
是吗 去干吗
Yeah? And do what?
像喂鸭子一样 傻傻坐在那里吗
Sit there like I'm feeding the ducks?
我能不能…谢谢你不理我
Can I... Thank you for ignoring me.
老实说 最怪的是
The weird thing, honestly, is.
完全感受不到他的存在
how much he's not there
这让我觉得很安心
I find that consoling.
肯道尔来了
Well, here he is.
大驾光临  -嘿 嘿 早上好
-Kendall Plus.   -Hey, hey. Morning.
早上好 抱歉迟到了  -嘿
Good morning. Sorry I'm late.   -Hey.
要带领我们得永生的人
The man who's gonna lead us to eternal life.
对  -韦斯达·耶稣
Right.   -Way star Jesus.
看到今天的民调结果了吗
Have you seen the polling today?
好吧 难怪你们精神这么好
Okay, that's why you're all perky.
很让人兴奋 你的红卫兵一定
Very exciting, I'm sure your Red Guards are all, you know
摩拳擦掌 准备逮捕思想犯
ready to come round up the thought criminals
把警察局变成拥抱派对
and turn police stations into cuddle puddles
让人兴奋的 不是第一行
The exciting part isn't the top line.
我在 阿拉斯加 人气暴涨
In Alaska, I'm exploding
四到六个百分点
Four, five, six percent.
好了 各位 可以切入正题吗
Right, guys, can we do this?
我今天很忙
I just, I have a lot going on today
没问题  -好的
-Sure.   -Very well.
我正式召集葬礼管理委员会
I hereby convene this funeral management committee.
已经把资料传给你们了
I've sent the materials
你们应该也都看过了
and I assume you've familiarized yourselves
因为我很担心
Because I'm concerned.
玛西娅的要求我们全都答应
We're saying yes to all Marcia's wishes
再来是你们的想法 老爸的遗愿
then all your ideas, Pop's requirements
葬礼有可能变成 为期三天的 哀悼马拉松
Danger the funeral could turn into a three-day grief-a-thon.
是啊 不要管玛西娅了  -我附议
-Yeah, just fuck Marcia.   -Seconded.
好极了 议案通过
Great.   -Carried.
尽管如此 我们还是希望 把时间控制在90分钟左右
Nevertheless, we really want a tight 90.
现在的核心问题是
And the central question is...
谁要致词?
who's gonna speak?
什么 对着全球势力最强大的 政治文化
Oh, what, in front of the most powerful, political, cultural
商业人士 致词吗
business interests in the world?
我随便
I mean, I'm easy
对吧 我可以讲爸爸的事
Right? I could speak about Dad.
怎么 你要讲你平常 诋毁爸的那些话吗
On what? Your usual malign influence material?
我可以致词
I could do it.
我认为 如果真的有人想干
I think if any one of us actually wants to do it
想致词 就应该说出来
do the big number, then we should just say
因为 大概 不会有人介意 对吧
because, probably, no one minds, right?
不是吗 对吧
No? Yeah.
好了 你们想一下吧
Okay, will yoUhave a think?
我要上数码战车
I'm jumping on the digital battle bus.
车尾派对 我们得搞定 对吧
Tailgate party, we nail it down, yeah?
好 再见  -没问题
Okay. Bye-bye.   -Sure.
好了 祝你好运  -再见
All right. Good luck.   -Bye.
说到这个
Right.
小西 我们…
So, Shiv, on the...
对车尾派对有个提议
One thing from us, on the tailgate
我们在想 要不要出于政治考量 邀请纳特
we were actually wondering about us politically inviting Nate
纳特·苏弗雷利吗  -纳特
-Nate Sofrelli?   -Nate.
好吧
Okay.
汤姆和我本来想
Tom and I kind of had hoped that.
为什么
Why?
因为在洛城很顺利
Because it went so well in LA
我要向这位世纪表演家致敬
You know, hats off to the Greatest Showman here.
抱歉我之前有点犹豫不决
And apologies on the old wibble wobble
必须要恭喜你 但是
and all due congratulations, but...
你们想要有个备用计划
Okay, so you wanna make sure we have a plan B
免得 不能用价钱逼退马特森
in case we can't chase Mats son out of town on price.
对 我们想在法规上做文章
Exactly, and we think that's regulatory.
祭出法规  -是
-We go hard regulatory.   -Yeah
司法部 贸易委员会 通信委员会 欧盟
DO J, FTC, FCC, EU.
不好吗  -就是说
-No?   --I mean... I...
我想 他们可能会叫停
I think they might just stop it
对  -但是...光是威胁
Yeah.   -But... but even just the threat
就能让马特森的风险大增
creates a ton more risk for Matsson,
让他放弃交易 对吗
kicks the deal down the line, right?
而纳特 他...
And Nate, he's...
他很了解对手
Right? He's across competition
而且 跟希门尼斯的人走得很近 所以…
and he's tight with the Jimenez folks on that, so.
可以找他来吗
Can we get him down?
假设 我们可以说服他 跳过那些说客和…
So we can sell it on a real level without lobbyists and all the...
正当法律程序
Due process?
那些事情  -对
That stuff.   -Yeah.
好 没问题
Yeah, sure. Fine.
可以吗 好的  -可以
Good? Okay.   -Fine.
好了 今晚见  -今晚见
-All right, see you tonight.   -See you tonight
我比你先
Beat you to it.
很好吧  -对 很好
Good, yeah?   -Yeah, good
我觉得很好 还有什么事
I think so. What else?
你觉得大举开除员工
How are you feeling about the, you know, blowback
造成的负面影响怎么办
from, you know, the firing?
那阵腥风血雨
The bloodlust?
要叫雨果去善后吗
Do you wanna throw Hugo at that?
不管了 敢做敢当吧
Fuck it, let's own it.
嘿 卢卡斯 是 听着
Hey, Lukas. Yeah, listen.
他们要在法规上做文章
So, they're gonna go regulatory
对
Yeah.
所以 你今晚一定要到
So, you need to be there tonight
不 很简单的 就…
No. It'll be easy. Just.
我爸生前邀请了你 所以…
My dad invited you, so...
对
Yes.
大概会有
There's gonna be, what.
40位左右 思想领袖 政客官员
40 thought leaders, pols, officials
那些握有决定权的人
who will actually decide this.
其中一半都会出席 好吗
and half of them are gonna be there, okay?
所以 我现在告诉你 你也必须到场
So, I am telling you that you need to be there, too.
跟他们对抗
To counter.
那么…嘿
So... hey.
我真的很难启齿
There's no easy way of doing this
这件事 我本周已经做了几次
I've done this a couple of times this week
老实说 有时 我真的是泫然欲泣
and sometimes, honestly, it just makes me cry.
但 我要真心地感谢各位
But I wanted to offer my heartfelt appreciation to you all
现在 请我的同事 格雷格瑞·赫许
and now I'm gonna hand over Tomy colleague, Gregory Hirsch
提供更多资讯
who has more information
谢谢您
Thank you, sir.
早安
Good morning.
我在此向各位通报 韦斯达·罗伊科
I'm here to inform you that Way star Roy co
正在估评几个方案
has been looking at a range of different options
以大幅减少开支
in order to drastically reduce costs
我们做了一个很困难的决定
and a very difficult decision
要重整泛美网科的国际运作
to restructure the ATN operation internationally
以保护未来的商业利益
has been taken in order to protect the future of the business
我们认真考虑过所有可行选项后
This action was only taken
才做了这个决定
after seriously considering all available options
如果各位参与了视频通话
But if you're on this call, this is confirmation
表示你们运气不好
that you are part of the unlucky group
公司会立即终止跟各位的聘雇合约
who are having their contract terminated
即刻生效
with immediate effect
理由是 裁汰冗员
on the grounds of staffing redundancy
今天是各位最后一个上班日
and today is your final day of employment
最后一个上班日
Final day of employment.
未来 韦斯达·罗伊科的
Going forward, we intend to operate
国际新闻搜集作业
Way star Roy co international news gathering operations
打算以第三方合约协议的方式进行
utilizing third-party contract-based arrangements."
我看到 聊天室里 有些人很困惑
I'm seeing some confusion in the chat.
对 我可能说得太冗长了
But yes, if I have been too wordy
对 我们要解雇你们所有人
yes, we are letting all of you go.
这次视频通话中 我显然不能接受任何提问
Obviously, I can't take questions on this call
但 这是令人悲伤的一天
but this is a very sad day
谢谢各位今天拨冗与会
And I thank you for your time today
和各位对韦斯达·罗伊科的贡献
and your service to Way star Roy co
再会
Goodbye
漂亮 搞定
Nice. Done.
好 贴了这个标签的德国酒
So, this German one with this label
你们要推这支 好吗
let's push this, okay?
说这是果香十足的淡红酒
Say it's a light, fruity red.
别说是生物动力酒 也不要说是德国酒
Now, don't say it's biodynamic, and don't say it's German.
就说是果香十足的淡红酒
Just say it's a light, fruity red
对 有一点气泡很正常
And yes, a little bit of fizz is normal
这是很优雅的口感 好吗
It's sophisticated, okay?
没关系 怎么回事 醒醒
It's okay. What's going on? Wakey-wakey
我...我很好
I'm just... you know. I'm fine.
只是累了 选前之夜
I'm tired, you know? Election eve.
好多事要忙  -是
-It's a lot.   -Yeah
其实这叫累前累
And it turns out, I'm pre-tired
我光是想到之后会多累 就已经累了
I'm tired about thinking how tired I'm gonna be
因为某人不让某人睡够觉
because someone isn't letting someone get a lot of sleep
真是对不起
Well, forgive me.
宾客名单多了几个人  -好
-So, we got a couple of extra names for the guest list.   -Right
马特森要来
Mats son is, in fact, coming now
为什么
Because?
因为 阿呆与阿瓜想破坏交易
Because Dumb and Dumber are trying to spook the deal, and.
用法规刁难他
wanna try doing regulatory shit angle
所以 他要来防患未然 所以...
and he's gonna come and head that off, so...
很好 这对我很好吧
Okay. Well, good. That's good for me, right?
是我上场跳舞的机会  -对
I mean, it's my chance to dance.   -Yeah.
我可以巩固我的位置
I could secure my spot...
对 当然  -在罗伊浩劫后的世界里 对吧
-Yeah, sure.   -post Roy-poc alyse, right?
还有 为了他们的图谋
Also, to push that agenda
他们想邀请...我觉得
they wanted to invite, and I didn't feel like I had
我不能拒绝
a tactical way to say no.
他们想邀请纳特
They want to invite Nate.
因为他是 吉尔和希门尼斯
Cause he's key on tech and trade
技术和交易的关键人物
for Gil and Jimenez.
对不起 我...
I'm sorry, I...
这不是…
It's not...
我真的很抱歉
And I am genuinely sorry. Really
没问题 纳特  -对
Sure. Nate.   -Yeah
能跟纳特见面也不错
It'll be good to see Nate.
我干吗介意
What do I care?
好的  -没事的
-Okay.   -It's okay.
谢了宝贝  -没事的
-Thanks, honey.   -Okay
好了 准备好要散布法规焦虑了吗
Okay, you guys ready to spread some regulatory anxieties?
当然 去散布监视资本主义的不安感吧
Yeah, sure, spread those surveillance capitalism heebie-jeebies, yeah?
小心 别被日报的专栏怪物堵到
Just don't let me get stuck with the Journal op-ed ogres
别这样 他们不全是
Come on, they're not all
加密法西斯和右派狂人
crypto fascists and right-wing nutjobs
也有一些创投民主党
We also have some venture capital Dems
和走中间路线的嗜血派
and centrist ghouls
爸的意识形态范围很广
Dad's ideological range was wide
要不要出击  -行 出击
Should we hit it?   -Yeah, let's hit it
走吧  -好啊
-Let's hit it.   -All right
强棒出击了 嘿 有啥好消息
Hitting it, hit it. Hey. What's up?
不是你们候选人的民调结果
Not your guy's poll numbers.
我看起来累吗  -不
Do I look tired?   -No...
也许有一点
Yeah, may be a little.
天啊  -要不要喝杯咖啡
Oh, man.   -May be drink a coffee.
现在喝咖啡的话 晚点就睡不着了
If I drink a coffee, then I won't be able to sleep later
用点脑子 格雷格
Think, Greg.
总之 听着 马特森要来
So, anyway, listen. Mats son is coming
那会是我的焦点
So, that is gonna be my focus
而你
And you, if...
除非你真要跟垃圾兄弟同一阵线
Unless you are truly aligning yourself to the dumpster brothers
最好也去拍拍他的马屁
you might wanna sweeten that beat, too
对 我也想大拍特拍啊
Oh, yeah, yeah. I'd love to... feather that bed.
但是 马特森讨厌我 所以 我想我是肯罗队的
But Mats son hates me, so I think I'm team Ken Ro
随你 格雷格
Up to you, Greg
好了 我要去交际了  -去吧
Okay, I'm gonna mingle.   -Yeah, mingle up.
谢了
Thanks.
很好 很好
Okay, okay.
看来小西找上薇乐莉了
Looks like Shiv's hitting Valerie.
你看到纳特了吗
Have you seen Nate?
没有 但是门肯的团队打来了
Yeah, no. But Mencken's team called
好 因为...民调结果吗
Okay. Because... the polling?
对 他们内部做的结果更糟 所以...
Yeah, well, their internals, even worse, so...
他们想干吗
And they want what?
要泛美网科大肆报道说 “我们要帮你们的枪做荷尔蒙疗法
ATN to go full " We're coming to give your guns hormone therapy
它们会变成女人?”
All your guns are gonna be ladies "?
康纳民调有百分之一的三四个州
Well, three or four states where Connor's one percent
搅乱了大局
are throwing things
可能会是选战的关键
You know, could be pivotal.
如果康纳退选
And, you know, if he were to drop out
大部分的支持者会转而支持他
most of the support would go to them
但 他的团队并没有…
But his team is not...
康纳阵营显然拒绝接触
It's just... They're just refusing contact, apparently.
所以 他们问我 能不能劝他退选
So, they've asked if I can convince him to drop out
我是说 我也不知道
I mean, I don't know
那小子可以去死 对吧  -门肯吗
-Fuck that guy, right?   -Mencken?
我想 对 胜利厢型车 还有欧马利那些混蛋
I think, yeah. Victory vans, those O'Malley fucks
我觉得他可以去死
I think fuck him.
跟他套套交情没有环处
I guess, I mean, it's not bad for us to be tight with them
说不定他会胜选 对吧
in case things swing his way, right?
好 我懂你的意思
Yeah, fine. I see you. All right. I'll hit the...
我去找那些弱智自由派 你负责那些纳粹
I'll hit the lib tards, you go help the Nazis
纳粹 没问题
The Nazis. You got it
等一下 不好意思
Wait. Excuse me
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿  -嘿 汤姆
-Hey.   -Hey, Tom.
你好 纳森尼尔
Hello, Nathaniel
谢谢你们邀请我
Appreciate the invite
我很想念你
Well, I've missed you
我不会待太久 说实话我很忙
I won't be long. A lot going on. Honestly
不会喝掉你太多酒
I won't drink too much of your wine
不 别担心 敞开了喝 伙计
No, don't you worry. You gobble my grav ad lax, pal
我准备了很多
There's plenty more where that came from.
这是果香十足的淡红酒
It's light and fruity
这种酒 能区分品酒家
and it's the kind of wine that separates the connoisseurs
和只在周末喝马尔贝克的白痴
from the weekend Malbec morons.
纳特 离这个人远一点
Keep away from this man, Nate.
离你远一点才对  -走开...
Keep away from you.   -Back...
走开 噩耗魔鬼  -不 你才是噩耗魔鬼
Back, foul news demon.   -No, you. You're the foul demon
很高兴看到你 算你狠
Nice to see you, Len. Good one.
混账
Asshole.
嘿  -抱歉打扰
-Hey.   -I'm sorry to interrupt
我可以跟他谈一下吗
Can I grab him for a second?
好  -谢了
-Yeah.   -Okay.
什么事  -就是
-What's up?   --Yeah, just.
你知道的
You know...
算是 其实很重要 而且有点让人措手不及
Yeah, yeah, kind of a biggie, actually, and a bit last-minute.
但 门肯的团队打电话来
But Mencken's team called
想知道 你可不可能...
and they wanted to know if you might be willing to...
就是…退出
you know, drop out.
退出选举吗  -对 退选
-Of the election?   -Yes, of the election.
你知道十小时后要开始播选情报道吧?
You are aware that the polls open in ten hours?
是 现在可能已经来不及
Yeah, so it might be too late
移除选票上你的名字
to physically remove your name from the ballots
但 你可以发表声明
But if you were to release a statement,you know
让你的支持者投票给门肯
divert the Con head stream to the Mencken river?
我流血流汗 又花了那么多钱
And after all the blood and treasure I've expended
我干吗要做这种事
why on earth would I wanna do that?
他们说 这是为了合众国
They said for the good of the Republic
是吗  -对
Yeah?   -Yeah.
对 所以…不要?
Yeah. So... no?
不要
No.
但他们授权我
Well, then, I have been authorized
对你提出 后续的提议
Tomake a follow-up offer,
那就是
which is...
你对摩加迪休很熟吗
How familiar are you with Mogadishu?
摩加迪休? 索马里首都
Mogadishu? In Somalia.
因为他们对你的才华异常佩服
Because they are very impressed with your talents
他们觉得你很适合
and they think that you'd be a good fit
担任大使
for an ambassadorial appointment.
感觉会被汽车炸弹炸死
A little bit car-bomb y
嘿 跟他们提议联合国
Hey, tell him UN.
好的,  -那比较对我的胃口 好吗
-Okay.   -That's more my vibration, yeah?
好  -可以吗
All right.   -Yeah?
好 我会跟他们说  -好的
All right, I'll report back.   -Okay
好 谢了-谢谢你
All right, thanks.   -Thank you
嘿
Hey.
你好吗 很高兴看到你
How're you doing? Good to see you
嘿 她露面了 很好
Hey. So, she showed. That's good
看来你安抚她了 对吧 佛朗哥将车
Guess you smoothed it over, right, General Franko?
没有 她还是火冒三丈
No, she's incredibly angry
好了 各位 各位
Okay, everybody. Everybody
欢迎大家
Welcome, one and all
肯 交给你了  -好的 多谢 汤姆 多谢 汤姆
-Ken, take it away.   -Okay, thanks, Tom. Thanks, Tom
谢谢 谢谢 好的 好的
Thank you, thank you. Okay, okay
好的 欢迎大家 欢迎欢迎
Okay, welcome, everybody. Welcome, welcome.
欢迎 好
Welcome. All right.
今天有谁来了 今天有谁来了
Who we go t here, who we got here?
卡莉·佛莱特
Carly Flight.
要命 播客女神  -好了 好了
Oh, shit. The pod goddess.   -All right, all right
大家皮绷紧点
Everybody watch out for her.
讲话要小心
Careful what you say
没错 是的 讲话小心
That's right. Yeah, yeah. Careful what you say
赖瑞 玛丽 很高兴看到你们,  -彼此彼此
-Larry, Mary, lovely. Lovely to see you guys.   -You, too
还有谁 还有谁来了
Who else is here? Who's here?
伦恩给的 伦恩也能拿走
Len. Len giveth and Len taketh away
各位小心伦恩
Watch out for Len
我兄弟 纳特·苏弗雷利 早上看到民调结果
My guy Nate Sof rell i saw the polls this morning
月球漫步过来了
and moon walked here
请代我们 问候吉尔和希门尼斯
Our best to Gil and Jimenez.
大家都来了 很高兴看到你们
Everybody's here. It's great to see you all.
这是第一次 没有老大的车尾派对
Yeah, you know, it's our first tailgate party without the big guy
对 但我们还是会狂欢的
Yeah. But we're still gonna live it up
照惯例 那里的甜爆米花.
As always, kettle corn over there...
会送去给最接近明天计票结果的人
will be shipped to whoever is closest to tomorrow's electoral count.
还有
And...
这个比较难
Yeah, this is a tough one
但 我们都会保持理智和友好
But we're all gonna stay sane, and we're all gonna stay friends
对吧
Yeah?
谢谢我妹妹主办这个派对
Thanks Tomy sis for hosting
多谢了 老妹  -应该的
-Thank you, sis.   -Of course
我们并不知道今年该怎么做
But yeah, you know, we... didn't know what to do this year
我们见证历史
You know... We watch history
缔造历史
We make history
有一天也会成为历史
And then, one day, we become it.
所以...
So, can I just.
我想请各位跟我一起
I'd just like to ask you all for a moment of silence, if we could
默哀一分钟
In memory
谢谢 谢谢各位
Thank you. Thank you, y'all
抱歉
Sorry.
没事 你好
It's okay. Hey, man
有贵宾驾到
So, VIP in the house
马特森先生 你好吗 欢迎
Mr. Mats son, how are you? Welcome.
谢谢 谢谢大家 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you, everyone. Thank you
这笔买卖 不包括我妹妹的房子
You know, you don't get my sister's triplex in the deal, you know.
所以 不要贪心
Don't get greedy
交易还没有敲定呢
Well, you know, hey, we haven't closed yet, so...
等着瞧吧  -很好 很好
We'll see, I guess, what happens.   -Nice, nice
总而言之 欢迎
Anyway, welcome.
家父很爱各位
You know, my dad... my dad loved you all
我们也是
we love you all
今晚玩得开心
so, let's... let's have some fun
狂欢开始吧
Let the games begin
干杯
Salud.
干杯 干杯 好的
Cheers, cheers. All right
好的 他来干吗
Okay. What the fuck is he doing here?
我也不知道 真的 这是在搞什么
Yeah, I don't know. Seriously, it's like... the fuck?
这枚炸弹会当场爆炸  -对 对
It's gonna blow up on the spot.   -Yeah, yeah
显然 是爸爸邀请他的
So, apparently, Dad invited him, actually
他进门前四分钟才用邮件答复 说要来
And he-emailed a yes, like, four minutes before walking in
四分钟? 好吧…  -对
-Four? Okay, well...   -Yeah
要不要赶他出去  -我也很想
Do we just throw him out, then?   -I would love that
但是不能让外人看到
No, but I don't think we can afford to be seen
我们如临大敌的样子
treating him as the enemy
我觉得 就挺下去
I think we hang tough. Yeah?
照原计划 用法规逼他
Just stick to the plan, regulatory
这里的这些混蛋
You know, these assholes in here?
都是我们的人
Our assholes
对 但他葫芦里在卖什么药
Yeah, but what's his fucking game?
他是会大吃一惊
Like, is he going for freak out
还是跟我们打相同的算盘?
or is he flicking the same beans as us?
你打算怎么做
Well, how do you wanna play?
说实在的...
Honestly, like, he...
我们之间有过太多摩擦
There's too much peanut butter between us
你能跟紧他吗
Can you stick close?
可以 没问题
Yeah. Sure.
不要让他接近高价值目标
I think just guide him away from the high-value targets
灌他酒 带他到处乱逛
refill his glass, run him in circles
背着他 跟别人 说他疯了  -这个简单
tell people he's Looney Tunes behind his back.   -Easy.
不要让他接近大人物
Keep him from the big wigs
所以 是重点打击计划
So, operation just, like, Nuke the Luke.
对  -好 这我做得到
-Yeah.   -All right. Yeah, I can do that.
好的  -来吧
Okay.   -Let's do it.
整死那个瑞典佬
Let's smash that Swede
我累了 有很多事要忙
I'm tired. It's a lot, you know.
选前准备很辛苦
Pre-election prep, you know
对 我想也是
Oh, right. Yeah, I be t, I bet.
是的 很辛苦
Yeah. It's a lot.
所以 你...
Hey, so, are you, like.
你在公司是负责实务还是监督
In the company, are yoUhands-on or more of an overview guy?
说来有趣 我想
Interesting. I guess.
我问你
Well, let me ask you this
你觉得哪种比较有价值
What would you value more highly?
认真的吗 不
Really? No.
因为我觉得 我两者都可以
Because I like to think that I could do both
我可以亲自动手 也能动脑
You know, I get my hands dirty and clean noggin and, you know...
可以一心多用  -好
Multi-tasker.   -Okay
你在拍我马屁
You're kissing my ass.
才没有 我没在拍你马屁 卢卡斯
No, I'm not kissing your ass, Lukas
你太聪明了 马上就会察觉
You're too smart, you'd spot it a mile off.
我正要在你老公嘴里拉屎
I'm about to take a shit in your husband's mouth
他八成会说
and I'm pretty sure he's gonna tell me
尝起来像红酒烩鸡
it tastes like coq a u vin
不会 我不会 我不会
No, no, I'm not, I'm not
说真的 你们家好漂亮
No, but seriously, it's a really, really nice place
多谢夸奖  -谢谢 谢谢你
-Thank you.   -Thanks. Thank you.
离婚后 房子归谁?
Who'll get to keep it in the divorce?
我们是不是要去交际一下  -对 很高兴看到你
-Yeah, shall we hit up some people?   -Yeah, good to see you
回头再聊  -好
-Talk to you later.   -All right
是的
Yeah.
很高兴看到你
It's good to see you
我也是 加里
Yeah, yeah. You too, Gary.
你要先找纳特 卡莉 和薇乐莉
So, you need to hit Nate, Carly, Valerie first
我得盯着我哥哥 你只需要...
But I have to keep an eye out for my brothers, and you just need
你有过经验 别...
You've done this before, so just don't...
你知道的 不要...-不要 什么
-You know. Don't...   -Don't what?
不要大叫“人都是资料"再把屌塞进鳄梨酱?
Don't scream "people are data " and stick my dick in the guac?
对 没错 不要...  -不要那样做 明白
-Yeah. Sure. Don't... Yeah.   -Don't do that. Okay
你即将买下 美国最有价值的文化资产
Yeah, you're about to purchase one of the most prized cultural assets
和政治通讯频道
and political communication channels in America
所以 得先打好地基
and you need to prepare the ground
否则 你的众多敌人
because otherwise, your many fucking enemies
一定会当你是哥特堡的混蛋程序员 而出卖你的
will portray you as some jerk-off coder from Gothenburg, okay?
我就是个哥特堡的混蛋程序员
I am a jerk-off coder from Gothenburg
对吧 艾芭
Right, Ebba?
还记得艾芭吗  -嗨 记得
You remember Ebba?   -Hi, yeah.
很高兴又看到你
Good to see you again.
你好吗  -彼此
-How are you?   -You, too.
我...你知道的 谁在乎啊
Oh, I'm, you know... Who cares?
谁在乎啊 是啊 真迷人
Who cares? Yeah. Charming
不是说你必须现在行动
Okay, oh, well, not that you need to do anything about this now
但 你应该开除你们的说客
but you should fire your lobbyists, just so you know
你们需要的是造雨者 而不是气象播报员
You need rainmakers, not weather forecasters.
当然 不过这不是我的职权范围
Sure. It's just not really my arena.
对不起 这个是安德瑞斯.
I'm sorry. It's more Andreas.
艾芭 你不用道歉
You don't have to apologize, Ebba, it's
我们只是在分享资讯而已
It's just information we're sharing, so...
这是...社交焦虑
It's... social anxiety
全世界唯一讨厌跟别人交谈的公关
The only PR person in the world who hates talking to people
对 我不爱参加派对 但是我没问题的
Yeah, I don't love parties, but I'm good
我则最爱派对
Whereas I love them
真的
I do.
干杯  -好极了
-Skal.   -Yep.
对 我有个爱吃大麻的二当家
So, I have a number two who's moon-beamed on edibles
和一个害怕沟通的公关主任
and a communication officer who's terrified of communicating
太好了
Oh, brilliant.
所以...我不去摩加迪休
So, Mogadishu's a no-go
当然  -去那里等于被判死刑
-Of course.   -It's a death sentence.
老实说 我们觉得受到羞辱
Frankly, we're insulted
但是...  -是吗
-But...   -Are you?
我想衡量所有的选项
I would like to roll through all the options
你身为我弟...
So, as a brother...
觉得最好的选项是什么  -好的
-what's the top option?   -Okay
让我看一下
Let me... Let me have a little look
我很想去欧洲
I would love to get to Europe.
有办法悄悄摸进去吗
Can I creep up through the underbelly?
从巴尔干半岛上去
Come up through the Balkans?
递补几个离职的资深外交官 圣诞节到柏林
Couple of senior departures, Berlin by Christmas?
他们也许会愿意让你去斯洛文尼亚或斯洛伐克
They may be willing to talk Slovenia or Slovakia
斯洛开头的国家我都不想去
Yeah, I think I'm a no on the Slos.
韩国怎么样
What about South Korea?
韩国
South Korea.
国内生产总值在十名之内
Top ten GDP
重要的地缘政治玩家
major geopolitical player
我觉得难度很高
I feel like that would be tough.
朝鲜
North Korea.
主上 别乱讲
Oh, easy, my liege
你又不知道 没人知道 这就是重点
You don't know. Nobody knows. That's the point.
说不定 我能重现尼克森打开中国大门的伟业
I could open it up like Nixon did China.
康 他们不会让你去核武国家
Con, they're not gonna put you anywhere with nukes
太羞辱人了 我不想去
Well, that's insulting. I don't think I wanna go anywhere
没有核武的国家  -好吧 那么...
-that doesn't have nukes.   -All right. Well...
你觉得阿曼如何
How do you like Oman?
阿曼
Oman?
对 贫穷版的沙特阿拉伯 或富裕版的也门
Yeah, poor man's Saudi Arabia or rich man's Yemen.
我得问问
I have to check.
看我家那口子觉得阿曼如何
See what my woman thinks about Oman
真有你的 很好  -很好
-Nice. Yep. Good.   -All right, good
我觉得 我是个白手起家的人
Well, I... I guess, essentially, I'm a self-made guy
推出了大受欢迎的超酷商品
who came up with a really cool product that people love
我会把每个月的九块九毛九寄给你
I... I send you my 9.99 a month
我不讨厌你  -感谢惠顾
-I'm no hater.   -Appreciate it.
但 丹尼尔很担心失控的算法
But Daniel is troubled by out-of-control algos.
他担心你们这些...  -是
-You see, he is worried that you...   -Yeah.
科技宅 会卯起来 做资料探勘
Bleep bloop guys are gonna data-mine us all to death
对 不 不 这我明日
Yeah. No, no, I totally get that
但 资产迟早会有人接手 对吧
And in terms of all this someone's gonna pick up the assets, right?
那 会是谁呢
So, who's that gonna be?
会是...我无意冒犯 小西
Is it gonna be, and no offense, Shiv
但是 要交给富二代吗
but the fail sons?
真的吗 这是个好选项吗
Really? Is that a good option?
他们会遵循父亲的老路 但是做法更笨拙
They will do what he did, but they will do it stupider
更难看 更没有责任感
and uglier, and less amenable
我知道很让人惊讶 但 卢卡斯还蛮愿意听取建议的
And, surprisingly, Lukas is actually pretty amenable
乐于接受建议?  -对
Amenable?   -Yes.
那 泛美网科的领导阶层呢
What about leadership at ATN ?
我会大刀阔斧地改革
Well, I would definitely make some major leadership changes
泛美网科的领导阶层 对  -真的吗
-at the top at ATN , yes.   -Really?
汤姆
Oh, Tom.
我挤不进去
I can't wiggle my way in there.
他拉着小西去拍纳特的马屁
He's just busy slobbering up Nate with Shiv.
格雷格 他们只是在聊天
They're just talking, Greg
你能不能多销几瓶红酒
Can you... Can you push a few more of these, and.
算了 先收起来
No, actually, put them away
咱们用饥饿营销
so we create a kind of scarcity thing
嘿 哥们  -嘿 哥们
-Hey, man.   -Hey, man
兄弟
Brother.
好久不见
Been a minute.
听我说 我知道咱们没有机会好好聊聊
Listen, I know we have n't had a chance to talk
我很遗憾 哥们
I'm sorry, man.
是啊  -他是个…
Yeah.   -He was...
我能说什么呢 天啊 我简直无法想象
What can I say? Jesus, I can't imagine.
是啊 很难过 但是你知道的
Yeah, it's tough, but, you know
日子还是要过的 对吧
life keeps a-rollin', right?
但是 你哥们
But you, man.
你很有造王者的架势
You, throwing off some kingmaker vibes
真的 丹尼尔还好吗
Fuck yeah. How's Daniel?
我可以推荐你几个人吗
Can I shoot you names?
我扑克之夜的牌友
You know, you could make a decent.
可以组成一个很不错的内阁
You could make a decent cabinet from my fucking poker night
当然 好 运动人士一定会很喜欢
Sure, yeah, yeah. The activists would love that
听着 兄弟 我就直接说了
Look, dude, I'm just gonna give you my rap straight
可以吗
Okay? Is that okay?
我觉得 我们会对你们很有帮助
I think we could be really good for you guys.
我说的是 大幅重整对话
Like, I'm talking major reset of the dialogue
这与我的利益有切身关系
Which I am personally invested in
但 前提是 这笔交易必须破产
But that only happens if this deal goes away
你懂的 碍于董事会和股东
Yeah, you know, board-wise, shareholder-wise
我们没有办法公开说
we can't come out publicly
但是 你应该要知道 这笔交易是行不通的
but the deal, you should know the deal is headed to the woodshed
Gojo的成长有自共赌 他也很有个人魅力
GoJo has had incredible growth, he's a charismatic figure
但他注定要出局的
but he's gonna get wrung out
而且 有一些事情值得担忧
And you know, there is really legitimate concern here.
法务部和贸易委员会 为了体育重叠的部分 而迟疑
DOJ or FTC balking at the sports overlap
通信委员会又不想让外国人拥有电视台...
the FCC over foreign ownership of broadcasts.
他在对我提案了  -我是说真的
-He's pitching me.   -No, I'm... I'm telling you
也许 外国投资委员会.
I think maybe CFI US
对马特森偏激的政治立场
might have a word to say about Mats son's, you know
和大屠杀笑话有意见
extreme political positions and fucking Holocaust jokes
当然 所以呢
Sure, so... so what?
你们很快就会修订法规
So, you guys come out for regulation pretty soon
我会让你们头100天很好过的
and we give you a better ride in the first hundred days
我都忘了 你在派对时有多饥渴
Man, I forgot how eager you were to get laid at a party
我回去问一下
Let me check in.
好的 我喜欢
Cool. All right. Love it
我确实很饥渴
Would love to get laid
可以回避一下吗
Can we have the room?
你做得很好 显然很有说服力
So, you're doing great. Yeah, eminently plausible
措辞很恰当  -真的吗
Nice wordings.   -Yeah?
真的吗  -真的
Really?   -Yeah
对 你做得很好  -那就好 那就好
-Yeah, you're doing good, yeah.   -Nice, nice.
我想纳特很喜欢跟你聊天
Nate, I think, really liked talking to you
卡莉爱死你了  -酷 酷
-and Carly loved you, so, yeah.   -Cool, cool
我本来还不确定
I wasn't sure.
我有时候 很难读懂别人的反应
'cause I don't always read people great, so...
放心 你表现得很好
Yeah, no, it's good. You're good
你已经跟精英团队聊过了
Yeah, you've hit the A team
现在 要去找
and so, now I think we should build your profile
写专栏的自恋狂 和首都圈的变态
with the op-ed narcissists and the Beltway psychos
好 一网打尽 我喜欢...  -很好 没问题
-All right. Bang... I like this.   -Yeah. Sure. Yeah.
我本来以为这些人会很复杂
You know, I thought these people would be very complicated
但并不是
but it's... they're not.
基本上 就是金钱和八卦
It's basically just, like, money and gossip
如此而已  -真的 就是这样
-That's it.   -Oh, yeah. No, that's all it is.
只是金钱和八卦
Just money and gossip
好  -这样就够了
All right.   -That's everything
好 带我去天堂之城
All right. Well, take me down to the paradise city
·来吧  -好极了
Let's do this.   -Great. Well
我想 现在 我应该问那个问题了
At this point, I think I would like to ask the question
不是说我不爱带着你
not that I don't love heaving you around
到处献宝 让你发光...
like a great lump of pine and making you shine...
但是...
But...
你最近又为我做了哪些呢
what have you done for me lately?
好啊 那…
Okay, well...
你要什么
What do you want?
我很喜欢跟你聊天 所以 你要什么...
I... I really like talking to you, so you can have...
尽管开口
you can have whatever you want.
好的 这个情况对我来说 不是没有风险
Okay, so, this situation's not without risk for me.
所以  如果我要积极地
So, if I was Tomove to actively engage
协助你完成并购
in assisting you with the acquisition
我必须知道
then I would need to know
未来 我会担任非常非常非常重要的职务
that it leads to a very, very, very significant role
连说三个非常
Three verys.
没错  -好 好
-Yeah.   -Okay, okay
请继续
Carry on.
我了解这家公司
So, I know the company
我什么都知道 我对它了若指掌
I know everything, I know my way around
我很有合作精神 我继承了家族姓氏
I'm collaborative, I have the name
我很厉害 而且蓄势待发 好吗
I am... I'm hot shit and I'm ready to go, okay?
好哦
Okay.
我可以想一下吗  -不行
Can I think?   -No
好吧
All right.
好 我...
Okay. I...
我不想失去你 所以…
But I would hate to lose you, so... so let's.
这个可以晚点再谈吗
Why don't we circle back in a bit?
好吗  -好 当然 没问题
-Okay?   -Yeah. Sure. Of course
好  -好
-Yeah.   -Yeah.
你在外面表现得很好  -好
You are doing good out there.   -All right
像是 有自学能力的 人工智能
You're like a self-teaching A I
我休息一下
I'm just gonna take five
然后 再回来找那些 混蛋和软脚虾
and then I'll be back with the dipshit s and limp dicks
好 没问题
Yeah. Sure
瘦皮猴
Boney Maroney
怎么了  -可以帮个忙吗
-What's up?   -Can you lend a hand?
马特森 你可以去照顾他吗
Mats son. Can you, like, look after him?
他过去曾经表达过厌恶
Yeah, I guess he occasionally has expressed a distaste in the past for...
我这个人
my particular flavor of me
给他一根大麻烟 或更猛的东西
Just find him a blunt. Or something stronger.
帮他找几个女人 好吗
Point his dick in the direction of some fissile material, yeah?
好 我试试看  -交给你了
-Yeah. Okay. I can try.   -You got it.
汤姆 你明天会威胁民主吗
So, Tom, are you going to imperil democracy tomorrow?
是 “你 靠墙站好 你也是
Yeah, " You against the wall, you against the wall.
你是个好人 留你一命" 其他人杀无赦
You're a nice guy. You can live." Bang.
少来了 拜托  -这就是我的工作
Oh, yeah. Come on, please.   -That's what I'll do
我可以保证 这位温和先生的辣度 只有一星
I can assure you, Mr. Mild here is a one-pepper menu item.
谢谢你 亲爱的
Thank you, dear.
交易完成后 有什么计划
And plans after the deal goes through?
听说 你另有高就
I hear you may be headed elsewhere.
你知道的 我永远有选择
Oh, well, you know, always got options.
为什么 你听说什么了
Why? What did yoUhear?
可能是我听错了
Well, maybe I heard wrong
抱歉 失陪一下 史考特
Sorry. Excuse me, Scott
真是一流的胡搞瞎搞
That is some top-shelf rat fucking there
对 再见
Yeah. Bye-bye
有什么劲爆好料吗  -他们挖了马特森的底
Got something juicy?   -Yeah, there's... On Mats son.
果然很劲爆
It's pretty juicy.
听说 他跟艾芭有一腿 就是他的公关主任
Apparently, he's been creeping on Ebba, his comms
寄了怪东西给她
sending her some weird shit
血液 头发
Blood, bits of hair.
也许还有别的东西  -太劲爆了
-Perhaps some other things.   -Num.
纳特 嘿 纳特  -对
Nate. Hey, Nate.   -Yeah...
你想听吗  -纳特 你过来听
You want in on this?   -You're gonna want in on this
纳特 想不想听坏人的丑事
Nate, you wanna hear something nasty about someone terrible?
马特森的秘密  -当然 我得走了
Mats son's shit.   -Sure. I gotta go
你要走了?  -对
-You going?   -Yeah.
但 那件事 没问题吧
Okay, but we're good on the... situation?
丹尼的人不太希望
Daniel's people aren't too comfortable
我跟你们打交道
with me rubbing shoulders with you
还有库柏...
And, you know, Coop.
这个大嘴巴
likes to yap, and
我跟你们走得太近了 所以...
Yeah, it looks a little cozy, so...
对不起  -好的 但是
Apologies.   -Okay, but.
这不是空穴来风
you know, I think there is something here
真的很让人担心
These legitimate concerns
你去跟丹尼尔说
You just tell Daniel, I mean...
我们可以帮你们保留黄金时段
we can make primetime safe for you
你们只要对市场...   -我就跟你直说了
All we need is one sentence...   -I'm gonna be straight with you
说句话就好  -这段对话的内容
-signaling to the markets.   -I don't feel comfortable
让我不太自在
with the tenor of this conversation
这段对话的内容 让你不太自在?
You don't feel comfortable with the tenor of this conversation?
别在我面前假清高 兄弟
Don't play hall monitor with me, bro.
好吗 我很了解你
Right? I know you.
我知道你是什么人 朋友  -肯
I know who you are, my friend.   -Ken.
我不知道你觉得这是什么
I don't know what you think this is
我不是吉尔 你也不是洛根
I'm not Gil, and you're not Logan.
这是好事
That's a good thing
再见
I'll see you.
我们在阿曼要住在哪里
And so, where would we live, exactly, in Oman?
应该是马斯开特的大宅院
In Muscat, I should think. In a compound
好的 是在地面上吧?
Okay, but would it be above ground?
当然 是在地面上 薇拉
Of course, above ground, Willa.
阿拉伯明珠
Pearl of Arabia.
好哦
Okay.
苏丹的话 等同于法律
" The sultan's word has the force of the law."
好极了  -在机场 我们可以直接通关
Great.   -The airport, we walk right through
你是为了门肯
And this is for Mencken?
我的亲戚朋友都痛恨门肯
You know, all my family and friends hate Mencken.
外交官车牌
Diplomatic plates.
你可以到处停车
You can park anywhere.
把车开上人行道
You can basically drive on the sidewalk
警察也拿你没撤  -开车撞人不是卖点
-The police can't touch you.   -Running people over is not a selling point.
该死的 格雷格  -嘿
-Fucking Greg.   -Hey.
嘿  -我的瑞典朋友们
-Hey.   -My Swedish friends
很高兴看到你们
Nice to see you.
该死的跟班
Fucking hanger-on.
该死的笨蛋
Fucking dingleberry
兄弟 我在发动魅力攻势
Dude, I'm on a charm offensive here
你能不能客气点
Can you be kind?
想不想一起坐?
Would you like to join us?
想不想滚蛋?
Would you like to fuck off?
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
说真的 奥斯卡 我会开除你
I'm serious, Oskar. I'm gonna fire you
艾芭 拜托 开除他 好吗
Okay, Ebba. Could you fire him, please?
可以吗
Can you?
抱歉 你是不是觉得很无聊
Oh, I'm sorry, is this boring you?
我看他阉割你何止100次了
I've seen him cut your balls a hundred times.
对 是有点无聊
Yeah, it's a little bit boring
你看他虐待狂的表情 根本是乐在其中
But look at him. Sadistic face. He loves it
没错  -他喜欢被开除
-I do.   -He loves being fired
我是很想开除艾芭
I would... I would like to fire Ebba, though
是吗  -对
-Yeah?   -Yeah
但是没办法 因为她
But I can't because she's
创造了一个 我没有办法
created and fostered this situation
随心所欲的情境
in which I find it very difficult to do what I want.
我不是说你是故意的
I'm not saying you've done it on purpose
但是很有意思
but it is quite interesting...
只因为我们搞过
that you have sort of tenure.
你就享有某种终生职位  -卢卡斯
Because we mingled.   -Lukas.
艾芭
Ebba.
我不知道你是不是在开玩笑 但是…
I'm not sure if you're kidding, but...
我可以帮忙
I could help.
你要的话 我可以开除她
I'd fire her if you want.
是吗  -对
Yeah?   -Yeah.
我现在就开除她
I'd fire her right now.
我最近 在这方面有点经验
I've got some recent experience in this arena
你愿意为我这么做吗
Would you do that for me?
当然 我马上办
Instantly. Sure.
就这么说定了 各位
It's on. Guys.
大家集合
Guys, gather around
这家伙要开除我的公关主任
This guy is about to fire my senior comms.
你也别生气  -这笑话好好笑
No hard feelings.   -The jokes are funny.
这笑话好好笑
The jokes are very funny
艾芭 别这样
Ebba. Come on.
卢卡斯 你知道吗
You know what, Lukas?
我还真希望你能开除我
I wish you would fire me.
艾芭
Ebba.
艾芭  -艾芭
-Ebba! -Ebba!
我们公司不希望员工是这种态度
It's not the attitude of the employee that we want at our company
你还好吗
You okay?
嗨  -我们刚刚看到…
-Hi.   -We just... We saw...
我们只是想确定...
You know, we just wanted Tomake sure.
来看看你 确定你真的没事
Check in, make sure you're okay. Like, on a human level
我们刚刚看到了...  -是的
-We... We saw...   -Yeah.
你还好吧
Yeah? Like, are you... you good?
我没事 真的不用担心
I'm really... I'm totally fine. Don't worry about it
那就好 听你这么说 我就放心了
All right, well, good. That's good to hear.
对...
Yeah...
太好了!  -他似乎是个很糟糕的人
Totally.   -He seems kind of awful
我们...
We...
他的形象完全是我们打造出来的
You know, we... we built his whole rep
他甚至不是真的程序员
He's not even a real coder
技术是别人给他的
Someone gave him, like, a box of tech
他只负责卖
and he took it Tomarket, you know
了不起  -是啊 真了不起
-Bravo.   -Yeah, bravo
我们只想说 我们很同情你
Well, yeah, we just wanted to say we sympathize with all the shit
我反正只待到二月 所以...
Yeah, well, I'll be out in February anyway, so.
真的吗 太可惜了
Really? That's a shame
这是因为...
And... is that because of the...
他寄给你...那些东西吗
Sending you of, you know... whatnots?
什么...不是…
What... No.
那是他现在最不担心的事
I mean... That's pretty much the least of his worries right now
好吧 那是因为...?
Okay. All right. Because?
印度  -印度 对
-India.   -India. Right
我好像知道这件事
And I feel like I know this
但是 细节是怎样
but what are the details here with that?
细节吗 好
The details? Oh, yeah
我可以告诉你们所有细节 没问题
I... I'm gonna give you all the details, sure.
这样啊
Right.
可以跟你要根烟吗
Can I get a... Can I bum a smoke?
没问题  -谢谢
Yeah.   -Thank you
不客气
Sure.
泛美网科宣称
So, ATN is saying
民主党正面民调 是极端造谣阴谋
'Dems'positive polls a radical misinformation plot."
真有种  -这样的用词比较辛辣
Ballsy.   -Like to keep things peppery
我们有提过他很累吗
I mean, did we mention he's tired?
是的
Yeah.
看来 他无法事事掌控
I guess he can't be across everything.
对吧 疲惫男孩
Can you, tired boy? Hey?
你去跟阿潘讲这件事
But you should call Pam on that
因为 这里的人 我都看不顺眼
'cause, you know, everyone here's needling me
那你去叫他们别再屁滚尿流了
Then you should tell them to stop wetting their pants
这我知道 汤姆
Okay, well, I get that, Tom.
但 你听说凤凰城的事了吗
But also, yoUheard about the Phoenix thing?
欧马利对竞选办公室丢汽油弹
The O'Malleys firebombed a fucking campaign office.
好可怕  -是爆竹
Scary shit.   -A firecracker
其实是两根用胶带粘住的爆竹  -打扰一下 抱歉
A pair of firecrackers taped together.   -Pardon. I'm sorry
可以借这位小姐,..  -当然
May we borrow your lady -Sure
一下下吗  -没问题 别介意我
for a second?   -Oh, sure. Don't mind me.
你猜怎么着  -凤凰城的事吗
Guess what?   -What, the Phoenix thing?
好夸张
It's pretty wild.
不是 是马特森的数目有问题
Nope. Mats son's numbers are funky
抱歉 你们在说什么
Sorry, what the fuck are you talking about?
艾芭全都说了 印度的数据有问题
Yeah, Ebba spilled. Screwy metrics in India
马特森兜售的数字 和南亚的泡泡粒一样假
Mats son has been peddling bundles of South Asian packing peanuts
什么 你是说 像…
What? You mean, like...
很大的数字吗
Okay, so, significant numbers?
对 应该是非常大
Yeah, yeah. We think so. Big, big
我就知道他是空口自话
I fucking knew he was a bullshitter
暴发户靠不住
I'm telling you. New money.
拿到新钞一定要检查
You gotta hold those fresh bills to the light
好吧
Okay.
操  -对
-Fuck.   -Yeah
你三天开除了100个人
You said a hundred scalps in three days?
对 100个  -外侄孙先生
A hundred.   -Mr. Nephew, that's.
好惊人的数目 我...
That's quite a number. I.
我以为你是家族里的窝囊废
I thought you were backwash at the bottom of the gene pool
但这实在不简单
but this is something else.
对 你低估我了
Yes, you underestimated me, and that's exactly
这正合我意 卢卡斯  -好像真的是这样
-how I wanted it, Lukas.   -I believe I might have.
你是怎么做的
Well, how did you do it?
不知道 反正就动手了
I don't know, I just do it
把刀架他们脖子上.
Just jackknife right in there...
是的  -直接割喉
Yeah.   -and slit their throat
事后的感觉应该有点糟吧
It must feel, afterwards, a bit... a little bit shitty, right?
其实并没有
Honestly, not really
人事部说 我是最适合这份工作的人
HR say s I'm the right guy for the job
因为我看起来很关心 但其实无动于衷
'cause it looks like I care, but I don't
你不是个好人
Not a good person.
其实我是好人 只是...
No, I am, I am. It's just...
但 该做的 总是要做 对吧
You gotta do what you gotta do, right?
真的吗
Do you, though?
嘿 她来了  -嘿
Hey, there she is.   -Hey
嘿  -欢迎光临小孩这桌
-Hey.   -Welcome to the kids'table
可以跟你谈一下吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
好 是不是要玩潜望镜了
Oh, yeah, is it time to up the periscope?
对 抱歉要拆散这个智囊团
Yeah, sorry to break up the brains trust.
你坐 我马上回来
You sit still. I'll be right back
面带微笑的屠夫
A butcher with a smile
怎么了
What's...
干吗跑这么快 失火了吗
Why... Why are we running? Is there a fire or what?
有可能
Yeah, there might be.
你的数字是怎么回事
So, what's your... What's happening with your numbers?
什么数字  -别跟我装糊涂 卢卡斯
-What numbers?   -" What numbers?" Lukas.
印度的吗
In... Oh, in India?
对
Yeah.
是艾芭说的 还是奥斯卡
Is this Ebba or Oskar?
好
Okay.
我们是...
Well, we... have a...
有点小问题 我们正在调查
There's a little issue that we're looking into
订阅人数可能是假的
with subscriber numbers being... being bullshit
不是假的 而是…
Well, not bullshit, but.
有一点点假
a little... a little bit bullshit
什么叫一点点假
What does a little bit bullshit mean?
也许我们发现了计算上的错误
Well, maybe we discovered a metrics error
高报了印度的订阅人数
that has overstated our subs in India
如果有两个印度 这个数字就合理了
Like, by quite a... Like, if there were two Indias, it would make sense.
什么叫 也许发现了
You may be discovered?
对 但是没有两个印度 只有一个
Yeah, but there isn't two Indias. There's only one India
没错  -这就...
No. Yeah.   -And it's...
说来话长 但...
It's just a long story, but it's, like, you know...
这是个新兴市场 一切都是未知数
It's an emerging market. It's... It's all wet cement. It's...
所以 现金和换股的交易
So, stock and cash deal
董事会有权叫停
the board would be well within their rights to pull out
这你显然很清楚
You know... You know that, obviously
所以 你要怎么...你打算…
So, how are you... Were you...
你想什么时候处理
When are you addressing?
你怎么处理
Like, how are yoUhandling?
我不会让
I'm not gonna... I don't...
我不要外国蠢猴子卖空我的股票
I don't want some foreign monkeys just... shorting me.
我讨厌让别人影响我
I don't... I don't like when people get inTome.
但这件事 迟草纸包不住火
It's gonna get out eventually
或是我们买下韦斯达 把这件事掩盖下去
Well, or we buy Waystar and it gets lost in the deal dazzle.
法务部和证交所...这…
SEC, DOJ... Is this...
这究竟合不合法  -我们迅速成交
Is this even legal?   -We close quickly
情况就会开始大好
and then shit will get crazy good
等到下一季数据  大概就会是真的了
By next quarter, the numbers will be real, probably
拜托...你不觉得很好笑吗
Come on, it's... it's kind of funny, though, isn't it?
我知道 情况很糟
I... I know it's... I know it's pretty bad
我知道情况很糟
I know it's pretty bad
对
Yeah.
但你能处理吧
You can fix it, though, right?
对啊 当然  -可以吧
Oh, yeah, sure.   -Right?
我再他妈造一个印度出来就好了
I'l I just build another fucking India
造一个印度出来 我喜欢
Love that. Build another India
这才是我的好女孩
Yeah. That's my girl
杀了我吧
Fuck me.
嘿 格丽
Hey, Gerri.
我猜猜 “给我一杯马提尼”
Let me guess, " I'll have a martini."
我们可以聊聊吗
Can we chat about stuff?
我有一些想法 需要你的忠告
I have some thoughts I might need your advice
不行
No.
不行? 拒绝我哦
'No?" Just no?
格丽...
Gerri...
干吗
What?
那件事...
The thing, that wasn't.
开除你的那件事 那不是真的
The firing you thing, that wasn't real
不是吗  -不是
-No?   -No
那只是我一时激动...你懂吗
Not... It was, like, in the heat of the... you know?
你懂的  -我不懂
You know.   -No.
你不懂 好吧 拜托
No. Okay. Well, come on.
咱们就聊聊嘛
Let's... Let's have a fuckin'chat, okay?
你向我解释什么是证交所的时候
I'll stand in a cupboard and jerk off
我可以站在柜子里打手枪 好吗
while you explain Tome what the SEC is, okay?
还不能开这种玩笑吗
Oh, really? No? Too soon?
你要我怎么做 道歉吗
What do you want? Do you want, like, a sorry?
我最会道歉了
I got a whole purse full of sor ries
对不起  -我退出了
-I'm sorry.   -I'm out
我不干了  -放屁
I'm done.   -Bullshit
爸一天到晚开除人
Dad fired people all the time
我当时只是一时兴起
I was just feeling kind of fire-ish.
听着 你该知道 我有一些要求
Look, I have some requirements you should know about.
其中一些已经正式传达了
Several of which have been officially communicated
有一些我觉得应该...
and some that I thought I should, you know
亲自告诉你  -好的
say in person.   -Okay.
格丽机器人出现了 好可怕,  -首先 我要钱
Robo-Gerri. Scary.   -First of all, I want money.
一大笔钱 好几亿
Eye-watering sums. Hundreds of millions of dollars
办不到 跳过
No. Pass.
我找了自己的名誉管理团队
So, I have retained personal reputation management
他们会在线上
and they will be on the line
监听卡罗琳娜 用我提供的纲要
when Karolina does her background briefings
做背景简报
off a set of my bullet points.
我会炸了你的纲要
I would set off your bullet points
如果未来五年 让我听到任何
And if I ever get a whiff of anything undermining my narrative
跟我叙事有所抵触的言论
any time in the next five years
我会告你们 并公开
I will sue and I will go public
大把大把的  -这太蠢了
-with those many, many pictures -This is so stupid.
你的生殖器的照片  -好的
of your genitalia -All right
照片都在我手上  -好极了
that I have in my possession.   -Great.
够清楚了吗  -是 非常清楚
Have I made myself clear?   -Yes, absolutely
跟你共事非常愉快 格丽 谢了
It's been a pleasure working with you, Gerri, thanks.
我本来可以拱你上位的
I could have got you there.
但现在不行了
But no
不行了  -不行了
-Nope.   -Nope.
再见
See you.
康 可以现在决定吗
Con, can we... Can we settle this now?
亚利桑那的政治汽油弹攻击事件
Everyone is quite freaked out
让所有人都惶惶不安
about this political firebombing in Arizona
凤凰城的爆竹事件
Oh, yeah, the pop-pop s in Phoenix?
对  -垃圾桶被烧的事情
-Yeah.   -The wastepaper basket on fire?
好像有个档案柜被送进重症监护室
I think a file cabinet was in the ICU
可以起草了吗  -事实上…
-Can we draft?   -Well, actually, there's been a...
我们改变心意了  -少来这套
slight change of heart.   -Get the fuck out of here
你已经争取到面子了 这条件很好
You got it. You got your bauble. It's great
来写声明稿吧
Let's write up a fucking statement, okay?
打开传真机
Wind up the old fax machine
传给你的怪人团队 好吗
and fart it out to your oddball army, okay?
罗曼 我们觉得
We wonder, Roman, if he might have
他为这场选举投资太多 不能现在退出
invested too much in his campaign to just, you know, drop out now
是的  -真酷
Yeah.   -That's so cool
你们努力过 但是失败了 现在必须往前走 找新目标
You tried, you failed, you move on, find something new.
他努力拼搏了
He's fought hard
我们想看看 会有什么结果
and we wanna find out what might happen, okay?
他可能会写一本关于这件事的书
-He might write, you know, a book about this
或是 去演讲...
Or a speaker circuit or.
嘿 什么都不会发生 好吗
Hey. Nothing is gonna happen, okay?
其实 明天什么事都有可能
Anything might happen tomorrow, actually
你真的这么觉得吗  -是的
Really? Anything?   -Yeah.
这就是我们所说的
You see, because that's the beauty
民主体制的美妙之处
of this little system that we have called democracy.
康 兄弟 就收下他们的好处吧
Con, man. Eat the fucking carrot, okay?
在场所有人都觉得 你是个狗日的笑话
Everyone in this room thinks you're a fucking joke.
叫你"老婆“闭嘴 遮住肩膀
So, tell your "wife " to shut the fuck up, cover her shoulders
打包去阿曼的行李 好吗  -罗曼 罗曼
and pack a fucking bag for Oman, okay?   -Rom, Rom.
我在讲话 没事的
I'm talking here. It's okay
别激动
Easy.
这里 有一个人 不把我当笑话
There's one person here who doesn't think I'm a joke
所以 我只听她的话 好吗
So, that's who I'm gonna listen to, okay?
真聪明 对啊 听她的吧
That's smart. Yeah, listen to her
薇拉宝贝   -怎么样
-Will a, honey.   -Yeah.
再见 很高兴认识你
Bye. Nice to meet you
这是我的荣幸 我一定会投给你的
A pleasure, sir. You got my vote. A hundred percent.
我只是想帮你 我只是想帮你
I'm trying to help you, man. I am trying to help you
好棒的派对
Really nice party.
好酷的家族
Cool, cool family
谢了 兄弟 尽管发推吧
Oh, thanks, man. Tweet about it.
今天晚上谁要在这个破地方出去玩
So, who's... who's going out tonight in this shitty fuckin'town?
有人吗
Anyone?
老实说 从上面鸟瞰这里 死气沉沉的
I gotta say, it's pretty depressing from up here
看得出来 这里像第二世界一样落后
You can really see how second world it is.
其实这里很热闹 很著名
I don't know. Pretty happening town, famously
真的吗 真的很热闹吗  -对
-Really? Is it, though?   -Yeah.
跟新加坡和首尔比起来
Compared to Singapore or Seoul?
这里简直是乐高乐园
It's like Legoland.
你知道我们还是老大吧?
You know we still run shit, though?
你是说 只限在纽约吧
Like as in only in New York
好 明白了  -好
-Yeah.   -Right. Okay.
纽约有的 别的地方也有
Well, nothing happens in New York if it doesn't happen everywhere.
你应该把这句话写在杯子上 对吧
You should get that written on a cup, right?
他这句话应该写在杯子上吧?
Shouldn't he get that written on a cup?
看起来 一定超酷
Like, that would look so cool
可以在鹿特丹的毒品专卖店卖
He could sell that in a... in a head shop in Rotterdam
说不定很有赚头
Could be a... a good business for you.
因为 我听说 你可能需要新的营收流
'Cause I hear you might need some new revenue streams.
是啊 对了 你的报告很精彩
Yeah. Hey, really, really good presentation, by the way
我好喜欢
Loved it.
我真的很期待那些预测
Can't wait to get into those predictions, man.
那些令人满意的预测  -是吗
Those meaty predictions.   -Oh, yeah?
一定会很好玩  -是吗 是吗
Yes. Gonna be fun.   -Yeah, yeah?
我也很兴奋 那些是估计 你知道吧
I'm excited about that. Estimates. You know, estimates
知道  -但你 兄弟
-Yeah.   -But you, man
你的数字爆炸性地好
Your numbers exploding, right?
好得匪夷所思
Like, literally unbelievable
谢谢 谢谢
Well, thank you, thank you
也恭喜你
And congrats to you as well
因为我听说你的数字很同志
Cause I hear your numbers are gay
我的数字很什么?  -同志
My numbers are what?   -Gay
我的数字很同志吗  -对
-My numbers are gay?   -Yeah
你们做了小小的估价后
You had this cute little valuation
数字就变成同志了
and your numbers just came out as gay
你的说法有点恐同耶
That's kind of homophobic, man.
让大浪打在身上
Dude, just let the wave hit you.
随波逐流吧
Float out
但是 我觉得 我就是大浪
I think I am the wave, though, actually
你觉得你就是大浪?
You think you are the wave?
因为你喜欢这笔交易
Because you love the deal?
开什么玩笑 这是史上最大的超额报酬交易
Are you kidding? Biggest overpay in history
我爱死了,  -好
-Love that shit.   -Okay
爱死了 爱到不行  -好
Love it. Love the deal.   -All right, well.
你爱到不行  -爱到不行
Love the deal.   -Love the deal.
爱死了  -来吧 来吧 兄弟
Love it.   -Come on. Come on, brother
我爱死这笔交易了
Love the deal, yeah.
对
Yes.
好的-爱死这笔交易了
-All right.   -Love the deal
爱死这笔交易了 爱死这笔交易了
Love the deal, love the deal
搞什么 丢人现眼的
The fuck? Bit of a show.
一抱泯恩仇
Hugging it out.
嘿 我走了…  -什么
Hey, I'm going to...   -What?
对 我收工了 我…
Yea h. I'm done. I'm...
我要去睡觉 我筋疲力尽了
I'm going to be d. I'm bushwhacked
眼皮重得要命
My eyes look sand papered.
行 再撑一会儿
Okay, well, you can stay up for just a little longer
一起跟客人道别
and say goodnight to people together
小西 你知道我明天有多忙吗
Shiv, do you know what my day looks like tomorrow?
汤姆 你明天什么都不会做
Tom, you're not gonna be doing anything
只是在找发亮的额头罢了
You're just gonna be looking for shiny foreheads
没事的 再撑45分钟就好了
It's fine, you can stay for 45 minutes more.
我只是有点累
I'm just a little tired
因为 我在家里举办的派对上
because all the fun gossip that I've been hearing from everywhere
听到好多精彩八卦
at this party in my house
说 我要被开除了
is that I'm gonna be shit canned
我对你有信心 兄弟
I got faith in you, man.
你一直忠心耿耿  -十足的信心
-You've always been a loyal servant.   -Lots of faith
对不起
Sorry.
你们只会帮倒忙
Not helpful.
你怎么了
The fuck is wrong with you?
我真的得睡一下
I just really do need to get some sleep
真的 对不起 到此为止 好吗
I really do. I'm sorry. Can we just leave it there?
你很累 我知道  -就当我没说
You're ti red. I get it.   -Please forget it
你一直念叨个没完
You keep on fucking saying
我知道你很累  -好 我累了
So yeah, you're tired.   -Okay, okay. I'm tired
就到此为止 好  -你到处说你很累
-Let's leave it there. Okay.   -You keep fucking telling everyone
好 我不讲了  -你很累 我知道
Okay, I'll stop.   -You're ti red. I get it
对不起 我只是...
I'm sorry. I'm just...
我只是很担心...
You know, I am just worried about.
也许我不该帮马特森
You know, maybe I've nailed myself to the Mats son cross
他可能只是纸老虎
and he might turn out to be bullshit
他反复无常...也许都是骗人的
You know, he's erratic and... you know, maybe he isn't real
小西 他是真的 他是未来
Shiv, he's real. He's the future.
不是 汤姆 他...
No, Tom. He...
他的数学里 藏了颗定时炸弹 我可能会被炸得粉身碎骨
There is a time bomb in his numbers, and I might get blown up.
你不会有事的
You'll be fine.
你一向能化险为夷
You'll always be fine.
不 不 我为了他 背叛我的家人
No. No, I am fucking my family for this
我可以说句话吗
Can I just say something?
这场派对上
At this party here
也许有40个美国最重要的人物
there are may be 40 of the most important people in America
而你 整个晚上走来走去
and you have just walked all around all evening
告诉他们 我会被开除
telling them all that I'm gonna get fired
不对 我只是略微暗示 那只是…
No, it was implied, lightly, as a little.
一个策略上的玩笑
part of a tactical kind of joke.
可以解释一下吗
Will you explain Tome?
那个玩笑 因为我听不懂...  -老天
The joke? Because I don't get...   -Oh, my god
笑点在哪儿  -汤姆
the fucking joke.   -Tom.
我听不懂那个玩笑  -那只是他说的假话
-I don't get the joke.   -It was something that he said
我们必须这么说
that isn't true, that we needed to say
但是 他说的时候 你站在他身达
But you stood by his side, and he said it
一言不发 满脸赞同
and you were like, " Okay. Well, that sounds good Tome."
真是够了 我现在不跟你谈这个
Fuck's sake. I'm not doing this right now
我现在是真的有麻烦 而那个只是在做戏
You know, I am in serious trouble. That was a play
你不会有事的
You will be okay
因为你是个悍婆娘
because you are a tough fuckin' bitch
永远都能存活下来
who will always survive
因为你会不择手段
because you do what you need
你会不择手段...  -你有听我说吗
-You will do what...   -Are you even listening?
什么我不会有事  -你会不择手段
-I'll be okay?   -You will do whatever you need
是吗 真的吗  -是的
-Yeah? Really?   -Yeah
你确定你没有影射吗 因为你说的是你自己
You sure you're not projecting? Because that is actually you.
我们是不是该 认真地谈谈
Should we have a real conversation?
跟蝎子谈吗 不用了  -那只是个友善的小礼物
-With a scorpion? No.   -That was a friendly thing
是啊 当然  -那只是个友善的小礼物
-Oh, yeah, sure.   -That was a friendly thing
你还真是很友善呢
You're real friendly
对 我是蝎子
Yeah, no, I'm a scorpion
你是鬣狗 是街头的老鼠
You're a hyena. You're a... you're a street rat.
不对 你他妈是条蛇
Actually, no, you're a fucking snake
是一条被当成领带的死蛇 汤姆
Here is a dead snake to wear as a necktie, Tom.
你为什么不笑
Why aren't you laughing?
我在想 是不是该把话说清楚
I wonder if we shouldn't clear the air
是吗 好啊  -对
-Yeah? Oh, sure.   -Yeah
我认为 你有时候很自私
I think that you can be a very selfish person
也认为 你觉得 很难为我着想
and I think you find it very hard to think about me.
什么鬼  -而且我认为
-What the fuck?   -And I think
你根本不该嫁给我
you shouldn't have even married me, actually
什么鬼话  -是的
What the fuck?   -Yeah.
你在说什么鬼话 是你跟我求婚的
What the actual fuck? You proposed Tome
你在我最低潮的时候 跟我求婚
You proposed Tome at my lowest fucking ebb
我父亲那时奄奄一息 我该怎么说
My dad was dying. What was I supposed to say?
你可以拒绝我
Perhaps no?
我不想伤你的心
I didn't wanna hurt your feelings
是啊 真是多谢了
Oh, thanks. Thanks for that
你去搞遍大人物的时候
Yeah, you really kept me safe
让我觉得好安全
while you ran off to fuck the phone book
少来 你是个乡巴佬
Oh, fuck off. You're a hick.
然后...然后...  -该死的保守乡巴佬
-And then... And then...   -A conservative hick
你还刻意隐瞒
yoUhid it because you were so scared
因为你被自己的丑态吓到了
of how fucking awful you are
你跟我在一起 也只是为了权力
You were only with me to get to power
你现在大权在握了 汤姆
Well, you got it now, Tom. You've got it.
我跟你在一起 是因为我爱你
I'm with you because I love you!
放屁 你上我 是为了我的基因
Bullshit! You're fucking me for my DNA
你上我 是为了往上爬
You were fucking me for a fucking ladder
因为 你们全家 都是没出息的小地方人
because your whole family is striving and parochial
你这样说不公平
That's not... that's not a fair characterization.
是吗 你妈爱我 多过爱你
Oh, no? Well, your mom loves me more than she loves you
因为她是疯子
Because she's cracked
你真的…想把话说清楚吗
You wanna... you wanna actually clear the air?
好 你背叛了我
Fine. You betrayed me
你打算眼睁睁
You were going to see me
看我去他妈坐牢 小西
get sent to fucking prison, Shiv!
然后 硬塞给我 难喝得要命的酒
And then you fobbed me off with that fucking undrinkable wine
还不肯生我的孩子
and you won't have my baby
因为 你实际上觉得
because you never even thought honestly
你跟我在一起 不会超过他妈的四年
that you'd be with me more than, like, four fucking years, I don't think
是你主动要去坐牢的 汤姆
You offered to go to jail, Tom.
你自愿坐牢 因为你奴性太强
You offered because you're servile
你就是…奴性太强
You just... you're servile
你除了自己 无法为任何人着想
You are incapable of thinking about anybody other than yourself
因为 小西 你的自我意识
cause your sense of who you are, Shiv
就是他妈这么薄弱  -是吗
-is that fucking thin.   -Oh, yeah?
是的  -这是你从书上看来的吗 汤姆
Yeah.   -You read that in a book, Tom?
你他妈一眼就让人看穿了 不用查书
You're too fucking transparent to find in a book
你太可悲了 你太可悲了
You're pathetic, you're pathetic
你是个受虐狂 但根本承受不了
You're a masochist, and you can't even take it.
我觉得 你没有办法爱人
I think you are incapable of love.
我觉得你应该
And I think you are maybe not
也不适合生孩子
a good person to have children.
讲这种话 太过分了吧
Well, that's not very nice to say, is it?
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起 但 你
I'm sorry, but you...
你无法想象 你对我的伤害有多深
You have hurt me more than you can possibly imagine
而你...
And you.
你夺走了 我原本 可以跟爸爸共度的 最后六个月
you took away the last six months I could've had with my dad
我没有  -就有
-No.   -Yes
你拍他的马屁 把我排拒在外
You sucked up to him and you cut me out.
你得不到他的肯定
It's not my fault
这不是我的错
that you didn't get his approval
我给了你无尽的肯定
I have given you endless approval
但你不满足 因为你心灵受创
and it doesn't fill you up because you're broken.
我不喜欢你
I don't like you.
我...
I don't...
我甚至不关心你
I don't even care about you
我不在乎
I don't care.
说清楚了吗
Have we cleared the air, huh?
心里好过了吗
Feel good now?
对  -对
-Yeah.   -Yeah.
太他妈爽快了 完美
Fucking great. Tip top
你配不上我
You don't deserve me.
一直以来都是如此
And you never did
因此而衍生了之后发生的一切
And everything came out of that.
太他妈无聊了
So fucking flat.
今天玩得还开心吧
You find ways to have fun out there?
还可以
More or less.
红酒闻起来像落水狗
The red wine smells like wet dog
听着 我想跟你聊五分钟
Listen, I just wanted to do five
就你跟我 就弗兰基和肯尼
Just me and you, just Frankie and Kenny
而不是执行长和主席
Not CEO and Chair.
不妙  -是的
No helms.   -Yeah.
我觉得 跟Gojo交易
I don't think the GoJo deal
不是对股东最好的做法
is in the best interests of the shareholders
我想讨论 阻止这笔交易的方法
and I would like to explore ways of blocking it
我不想听 肯
I don't want to hear it, Ken.
如果我告诉你
What if I told you
他在印度的订阅人数严重注水呢
his subs in India are significantly inflated?
我有个提议
I'm just gonna hit you with this
不如反其道而行
What if we run it all the way back?
我想知道那是什么意思吗
Do I even wanna know what that means?
以其人之道 还治其人之身
We go reverse Viking.
杀进他的老巢
We pillage their village
韦斯达并购GoJo
Way star acquires GoJo
那必须要有很严重的问题才行
It... There would have to be major issues
确实有
There are.
如果可以放慢速度呢
But if we could slow this down
我们吃掉马特森的午餐...
and we eat Mats son's lunch
变得比爸爸更强
bigger than Dad ever was
那 罗曼和小西呢  -我不知道
Roman and Shiv?   -Yeah, I don't know.
他们只是我计划的一部分
Part of my plans.
我爱他们 但是并不欣赏他们
I love them, but not in love with them, you know?
只有一个人能戴上皇冠
One head, one crown.
但是我需要后盾
But I'll need ballast
你挺我吗
Are you with me?
嗨 各位 嗨
Hi, everyone. Hi.
我要睡觉了
Bedtime for Bonzo
对不起 但请滚出我家
Sorry, but please get the fuck out of my house now.
真的 不... 拜托
Yeah, no... Please.
派对结束了 因为我要睡觉
Party's over 'cause I've gotta sleep
今晚好尽兴 太感谢了
It's been a terrific night. Thank you so much
不 我是说真的
No, I'm serious.
大家回家睡觉吧
Off you go. Go to bed
享受温暖的床 回家哭泣
Enjoy your beds. Go home. Cry
我不行了 我不行了
I'm done, I'm done.
我连站都站不稳 我玩够了
I can barely stand, but I've had enough
晚安
Good night.
晚安 汤姆  -别忘了拿外套
Good night, Tom.   -Don't forget your coats
去他妈的汤姆  -对 去他妈的汤姆
-Fuck Tom.   -Yeah. Fuck Tom.
去他妈的汤姆
Fuck Tom.
两位...
So, guys...
葬礼的事 如果你们没有意见
Funeral, if nobody wants to grab it
我想 就由我来致词
I'm happy to take the big energy spot.
是吗  -好
Yeah?   -Yeah.
我是说 看样子你们都没有兴趣
Yeah, I mean, it seems like nobody wanted it.
就让我来好了 好吗
So, I got it. Yeah?
当然 没问题 交给你
Sure. It's fine. Knock yourself out
尽情发挥吧
Just paint it red
是吗 你同意吗  -对...
Yeah? Happy?   -Yeah.
你呢  -同意
Yeah, happy?   -Happy
同意
Happy
皆大欢喜
Happy, happy headbangers.
那就决定了 好的
Here we are. Okay.
晚安  -晚安
Good night.   -Good night
晚安
Night.